<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brick Schema</title>
    <link>https://brickschema.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brick Schema</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 21:40:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://brickschema.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/schema/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 21:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/schema/</guid>
      <description> Version 1.0.3
 Version 1.0.2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 15:07:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/download/</guid>
      <description>Brick Downloads Brick consists of several TTL (&amp;ldquo;Turtle&amp;rdquo;) files. Latest version (v1.0.2) available here:
 Brick.ttl: Brick classes and tagsets BrickFrame.ttl: Brick relationships BrickTag.ttl: Brick tags (internal) BrickUse.ttl: Brick uses relationships (internal)  Past releases are available on GitHub
Brick Papers and Presentations  BuildSys 2016 Paper BuildSys 2016 Presentation BuildSys 2016 Demo Abstract BuildSys 2016 Poster  Brick Building Examples Example buildings represented in Brick:
 Gates Hillman Center  Location: Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA, USA BMS: Automated Logic Controls Built: 2009 Size: 217,000 sq ft Number of points: 8,292 Tagsets mapped: 99% Number of Relationships: 35,693  Rice Hall  Location: University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA, USA Built: 2011 Size: 100,000 sq ft Number of points: 1,300 Tagsets mapped: 98.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Development</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/source/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 15:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/source/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Development of the Brick Schema can be found on GitHub
 Brick TTL files Example Buildings Example Applications  Brick is created from collective efforts.
Process The Brick schema files were generated by:
 Identifying necessary terminologies from existing building metadata and modern applications. The result is the Building application list. Organizing the terminologies into Tags/Tagsets in a spreadsheet. The result is the Schema Engineering Sheet Converting the spreadsheet into Turtle files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/structure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 15:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/structure/</guid>
      <description>Brick is a uniform schema for representing metadata in buildings. Our schema defines a concrete ontology for sensors, subsystems and relationships among them, which enables portable applications. We demonstrate the completeness and effectiveness of Brick by using it to represent the entire vendor-specific sensor metadata of diverse buildings across different campuses, each comprising thousands of data points, and running complex unmodified applications on these buildings.
Brick Concepts Our research paper describes the Brick design and development in depth (link to paper).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interact</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/interact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2016 18:30:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/interact/</guid>
      <description> Graph Visualization
A visualization of metadata mapped to Brick schema from five example buildings  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 15:15:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/contact/</guid>
      <description> Developer Forum
We will actively respond to any concerns or questions. Github Issues
Any technical features can be discussed. We welcome any proposals including new Tagsets and feature.  The lead maintainers for Brick are:
 Gabe Fierro Jason Koh  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BuildSys 2017</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/buildsys2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 15:21:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/buildsys2017/</guid>
      <description>You can run the tutorial yourself using the IPython Notebook!
Tutorial We&amp;rsquo;re running a tutorial at BuildSys 2017!
A unified metadata schema has an important role in building operation and application interoperability. Brick is a unified metadata schema born from a BuildSys community’s effort on advancing technologies for the built environment. We propose a tutorial session for BuildSys attendants to learn about how to use Brick in their real systems and promote more involvement in Brick development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema version 1.0.2</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/schema/1.0.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 21:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/schema/1.0.2/</guid>
      <description> Schema Files (Turtle format)  Brick TagSet file Brick Meta Structure file
 Brick Tag file Brick Use file  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schema version 1.0.3</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/schema/1.0.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 21:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/schema/1.0.3/</guid>
      <description> Schema Files (Turtle format)  Brick TagSet file Brick Meta Structure file
 Brick Tag file Brick Use file  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brick</title>
      <link>https://brickschema.org/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 15:21:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brickschema.org/</guid>
      <description>A Uniform Metadata Schema for Buildings Commercial buildings have long since been a primary target for applications from a number of areas: from cyber-physical systems to building energy use to improved human interactions in built environments. While technological advances have been made in these areas, such solutions rarely experience widespread adoption due to the lack of a common descriptive schema reducing the now-prohibitive cost of porting these applications and systems to different buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>